BROOKE KUMAR

PROJECT MANAGER . WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT INFORMATION

phone: +1 (651) 399-3097

email: mrsbrookekumar@gmail.com

address: 120 13th Ave NE, Apt 212, Minneapolis, MN 55413

GitHub: brookekumar.github.io

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/brooke-kumar

OBJECTIVE

Experienced Program Analyst and Manager successful at cross- functional collaboration and project execution. Specializing in empowering others through dedicated consistency and delivery with an emphasis on buy-in and trust building. Self-motivated professional with proven results excited about career growth.

CERTIFICATIONS

- Intermediate Excel, Microsoft 2016
- PMP (anticipated January 2020)
- Full Stack Coding (anticipated March 2020)

HIGHLIGHTED SKILLS

Microsoft Suite • PMP (Microsoft) • Report analysis • Project planning • Advanced MS Project • Gap assessment • Presenting to large groups (50+) • Advanced data visualization • Spotfire • Web Development (HTML, CSS, JS, API integration) • Stakeholder success • Cross-functional collaboration • Project monitoring and execution

WORK HISTORY

PD Program Management Specialist

MEDTRONIC

DECEMBER 2017 - PRESENT

- Work with functional groups to advocate for alignment across projects within a \$25M/year remediation portfolio
- Lead project completion efforts across all functional groups -Create tools to drive consistency and reporting for extended
- team members and executives

Business Analyst

ABBOTT

APRIL 2017 - DECEMBER 2017

Regulatory Affairs Specialist

DAVITA CLINICAL RESEARCH FEBRUARY 2016 - FEBRUARY 2017

I have a passion for leveraging Program Management fundamentals to lead functional teams to success from planning to execution. I also have experience implementing tools to execute projects within a portfolio.

EDUCATION'

University of Minnesota

CONTINUING STUDIES, MINNEAPOLIS, MN CERTIFICATE, FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT

Carthage College

COLLEGE OF LIBERAL ARTS, KENOSHA, WI BA IN RELIGIOUS STUDIES, CLASS OF 2014

- cum laude
- Outstanding thesis, Humanities department
- Outstanding thesis, Religious Studies department